

SILVIA VENEGAS

Frontend Developer

CONTACT

silviavg96@gmail.com

692 980 521

in Silvia Venegas Garcia

46970, Alaquás, Valencia

EDUCATION

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING HIGHER DEGREE COMPUTER SCIENCE: DEVELOPMENT WEB APPLICATIONS

2016-2018

Solvam Vocational Training Center

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING MEDIUM DEGREE COMPUTER SCIENCE: MICROCOMPUTER SYSTEMS AND NETWORKS

2014-2016

Solvam Vocational Training Center

IT SKILLS

HTML5 - CSS3 - Sass - BootStrap - UIKit - Tailwind Css

JavaScript - JQuery - Vue.js - NodeJS -

Javel JS - Axios - Ionic - Angular 8 -

Android Studio - Capacitor

PHP - AJAX - Go

Symfony - Codelgniter - CakePHP

SQLite - MariaDB

Git - Docker

Adobe Photoshop - Illustrator - Adobe xd

Figma

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Mother tongue English: B1 - Proffessional competence

ABOUT

I'm a passionate person about the digital world.

I feel like I have the curiosity to learn new technologies, being always on the edge and improve my knowledge in the development field, and in other digital fields as well.

I enjoy programming, for me, it's more than a job, it's a lifestyle.

I'm self taught, disciplined, decisive and a team player person.

I can't wait to use all my experience and create big things.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - LEAD FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Sesame Time | Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 | Feb 2020 - Present

- API development with CakePHP + custom document panel.
- Setup and architecture design of the new Vue.js project.
- Custom development of the UI in a SaaS model.
- Development of Vue.js components, both renderless and specific.
- APP development with Capacitor (Ionic).
- Consumption of private/public API for development and data management.
- Integrations with third party API's.
- Troubleshooting.
- Management and direct training of a team of 8 people (Frontend team).
- Task and resource management with Scrum methodology.
- FrontEnd team, involved in all the selection process.
- Product management and organization for a team of 17 people.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Celebrand | Mar 2017 - Jul 2017 / Feb 2018 - Jul 2019

- Web design and layout with responsive adaptation.
- Custom development of CMS WordPress/Woo-Commerce, Prestashop.
- Custom development of modules/plugins (WP-PS).
- Custom backend development of comprehensive projects.
- Database design and management, user management, administration panels, landing pages, API's, connector management.
- PWA development (Progressive Web Apps).
- Management and integration of payment platforms.
- Management and integration of ERP systems.
- Management and monitoring of projects with end customers.

SILVIA VENEGAS

Frontend Developer

CONTACT

silviavg96@gmail.com

692 980 521

in Silvia Venegas Garcia

🖒 46970, Alaquás, Valencia

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Revi.io | Mar 2017 - Jul 2017 / Feb 2018 - Jul 2019

- Development of opinions system for CMS and custom integrations.
- Corporate website design and layout.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

DocuLand Reprographics and Scanning Bureau (London) | May 2016 - Ago 2016

Development of own Marketplace as well as the commercial pages of the company. Plan and organize the technical development of websites. Guarantee the usability of the tools used. Manage eCommerce daily. Optimize websites with SEO positioning techniques. Design of logos, corporate images, business brochures, etc.

IT SUPPORT

YMANT SERVICIOS INFORMÁTICOS, S.L. | Mar 2015 - May 2016

- Equipment maintenance.
- Support and resolution of technical problems online.
- Management of diagnostic software tools and other troubleshooting techniques.
- Carrying out quality controls.
- Relations with suppliers.

OTHER DATA

Driving license - B. Own vehicle.

